♪
[CLAIRE] Princess Iris,
I've taken care
of all the arrangements.
Henceforth, Sir Kazuma
is now a guest of the...
So, darkness was naked
except for a towel,
- and that's when she...
- Huh!
And that's when she?
[KAZUMA] Well.
[IRIS] Go on!
You must tell me
what happened next!
You wretch!
What are you filling
her mind with?
Are you trying to get cut down?
Hey, she wanted
to hear the story!
Have you forgotten her title?
You must call her
"the princess!"
[KAZUMA]
What a pain in the ass!
It's all right, Claire.
I told him that he could
call me by my name.
But, Princess Iris...
[sighs]
More importantly,
what did Lalatina do
while clinging to her towel?
[CLAIRE] You have to stop!
This tale is not fit
for royal ears!
Sir Kazuma.
I ask you not to fill
Princess Iris's head
with those kinds of stories.
Huh.
I'm sorry.
[KAZUMA] She actually
listens to people here.
[sighs]
[KAZUMA] Sure, in that case.
[BOTH] Huh.
I can tell you about the time
I beat Darkness in a bet
where the loser would go
through some crazy stuff.
Yes, by all means
I must hear more!
Oh no! Princess, do not
listen to a word he says!
[CLAIRE] He's no good,
no good at all!
[chuckles]
[KAZUMA] Okay are you ready
to learn what to do
when you've been swallowed up
by a Giant Toad.
The first thing you'll wanna...
This pretty much
sums things up.
[RAIN] We welcome you, Kazuma.
And we sincerely hope
that you will make yourself
at home here.
This will be your
private bedchamber.
[humming]
[KAZUMA] Ah, hey, miss,
could I have a word with you?
My name's Rain.
Listen, "Rain,"
this is a kidnapping, right?
You've been welcomed here
as our honored guest.
So, of course it isn't.
Ah, come on, it totally is!
[humming]
This is rather unusual
for Princess Iris,
as she's normally
quite obedient.
[RAIN] But since she so rarely
makes any selfish demands,
I must implore you to try
and humor her for a bit.
I get it, but still.
[humming]
- Huh.
- [whispering]
Huh.
I'm sorry.
All of the fun Lalatina
seems to have
made me a little jealous.
[RAIN] "I only ask that
for just a few short days
you agree to keep me
company as well," she says.
[chuckles]
[KAZUMA] Aw, ain't that cute?
♪
- [KAZUMA] Understood.
- [gasps]
So, Rain, could you
let my friends know
that I'll be sticking
around here for a while?
- Huh.
- [gasps]
[IRIS] A culture festival,
that sounds really fun!
Running a shop
with other people my age
sounds just wonderful!
But that said,
it might be fairly difficult...
[KAZUMA] She likes
hearing about school
a whole lot more
than I thought.
In those days, I was actually
bored outta my mind.
But it seems like
the princess here
is actually jealous.
If it sounds that good,
then why don't you
open up a school?
[gasps]
Hm.
[SPEAKER 03-A (F)]
Devil King Army alert.
The knights
are to mobilize at once.
They're back?
Huh...
With the way things
are these days,
it's not a good time
to immerse myself in studies.
[laughs]
- [sighs]
- [explosion]
[KAZUMA]
Now that I'm thinkin' about it,
this world has that Devil King
guys mess to deal with.
[SPEAKER 03-A (F)] The covert
raid by the Devil Kings army
has now been suppressed.
Any adventurers who contributed
should speak to the guild
receptionist for your reward.
[KAZUMA] Sneak attacks
on the royal capital?
The hells up with this country?
The Japanese expat
cheaters around here
oughta carry their weight
a little more!
- [IRIS] Thank you.
- Huh.
Those were
some amazing stories.
You can speak to Rain
about being teleported
back to Axel, tomorrow.
Even the castle
isn't completely safe now.
[sighs]
[KAZUMA] She's right.
And it's not like
I can defend this place
if I do stick around.
Though it's been insane.
I'm sure
those three goofs in Axel
- are probably worried about me.
- [AQUA] Kazuma.
[KAZUMA] I hate to leave,
but I guess I'd better.
One day could you tell me more
of your great adventures?
Of course I will.
I'll come see you again, Iris.
Huh.
[giggles]
Something about you reminds me
so much of my older brother.
[Kazuma gasps]
Although I wish I could,
the two of us don't get
to speak like this anymore.
And, while I'd like for you
to stay here even longer,
I know I mustn't be selfish.
[KAZUMA] What did you say?
Hm.
Oh, uh, well,
I just wish that you could
stay here a little longer.
[KAZUMA] Nah, not that part.
So, what is it, exactly,
that I remind you of?
Just, uh, just how it used to
be with my older brother and...
[KAZUMA] Would you take it
from the top, please?
Y-you're like my older brother.
[KAZUMA]
Again, but if you could do it
more casually, that'd be great.
[gasps]
Hm.
[sighs] Huh.
You're like my big brother?
[groaning]
[KAZUMA] And that's when I
decided to stay at the castle!
[birds chirping]
♪
[groaning]
Huh.
♪
[clapping]
[door opens]
Kazuma, sir, you rang for me?
I would like my morning coffee,
please, Sebastian.
[HEIDEL]
My name is Heidel, sir.
If you could, Heidel.
[MARY] Um, I was going
to make your bed.
Of course,
don't worry about me, Mary.
[MARY] Oh, right.
[grunting]
- [door opens]
- Huh.
Y-you're awake, good morning.
Big Brother.
[KAZUMA] Yes, I love it!
Being called
"Big Brother" is awesome!
[grunting]
♪
Good morning, Iris.
I think you need
to put some pants on!
[KAZUMA] Huh.
[groaning]
Look Iris, it's not
what you think, all right?
Your big brother
isn't some kind of pervert!
- I swear!
- Of course I understand!
Please, elder brother,
finish putting on your pants.
Please call me
"Big Brother," all right?
It feels like you're pulling
away and that kills me!
[grunts] Iris, wait up!
Iris, please come back here!
[KAZUMA] And just like that
Iris stopped calling me
"Big Brother."
♪
As for what
happened after that.
Wed play a little
hide-and-seek.
Some games of tag, too.
And every once and a while,
when I knew
she was sitting in class,
Id disrupt her lessons.
Basically, I was spending
my days as her playmate.
So, uh, I was hoping you
would play this game with me.
- Please?
- [munching]
[KAZUMA] I could tell
she still seemed embarrassed
to ask for things sometimes.
Guess Rain wasn't
kidding around when she told me
Iris was usually
pretty reserved.
Hmm.
[KAZUMA] One things for sure.
I definitely get
the feeling Iris knows
the people around her
are at her mercy
and do whatever she wants.
[swallows]
There's no way
I'm letting you win.
'Cause if were playing,
were playing for keeps!
You still wanna do it?
Ha!
I-I do!
I want to take this
really seriously, too!
Sounds good, just don't cry
if you're a loser!
♪
[KAZUMA] Now, to do this
the right way,
etiquette comes first!
Let's have a good game.
Yes, let's have a good game.
U-um, maybe we
ought to call it a day?
So you wanna win and run,
is that it?
I thought you were
playing this for real!
Don't start holding back
just 'cause you wanna
stop playing, either!
I can tell if you lose
on purpose, understand me?
I realize that this was all
my idea in the first place,
but you are being
a colossal pain, Elder Brother!
[laughs]
I win, baby!
You are extremely childish,
Elder Brother.
Oh, trash talking
after your big loss?
Well, I guess you still
earned this bamboo copter.
[IRIS] Ah, thank you so much!
♪
Aah! [chuckles]
We should head out and play
with that next time around.
Huh.
- Hm.
- Hm?
You really need
to get outside more.
Take it from me you never know
when you might run
into a friendly
neighborhood demon
or maybe a lich
that can survive entirely
off of bread crusts.
Huh. Please don't make
fun of me just because
I'm a little sheltered!
There's no way devils or liches
like that could exist!
[IRIS] Besides...
Huh.
If I were ever to leave
these castle grounds,
it would require an escort
of royal guards
with me at all times.
[grunts]
♪
Hm.
[KAZUMA] Konosuba.
[birds chirping]
♪
[groaning]
Huh.
♪
[clapping]
[door opens]
Kazuma, sir, you rang for me?
I would like my morning coffee,
please, Sebastian.
[HEIDEL]
My name is Heidel, sir.
If you could, Heidel.
[sighs]
[KAZUMA]
It's been a week, already.
Won't be much longer
before Mary the Maid comes in
to change the sheets. Hm.
However, shall I make
her job more difficult,
as any noble would?
- [knocking on door]
- Huh.
Here she comes.
♪
Ah, good morning, Mary!
I know you're ready to do
the old sheet swap,
but it's not gonna be quite
so easy for you this time.
Now, if you want to make some
quick work of this little task
then you have to say
"Master, I beg you
please allow me to collect
the sheets with your..."
[robe flutters]
♪
What is being
collected, exactly?
May as well finish
your thought, go on.
You have our
undivided attention, now.
Finish what you were saying.
[KAZUMA] Ma...
Master please allow me...
to collect the sheets
with your scent on them so.
[DARKNESS] "The sheets with
your scent on them so" what?
I thought you were an expert
at sexually harassing people.
Stop acting embarrassed
and say it.
Ple... Please. Hang on!
Why are you guys even here?
To drag you back home
with us, obviously!
Megumin has been
so worried
that she could
barely even sleep!
That was only a coincidence!
There's no need to cause
any weird misunderstandings!
I'm promoted
to Iris's playmate!
Finally, I've got
some stability and safety!
So, you can all buzz off!
You imbecile,
that is not an official duty
in this country!
Listen, this is totally unfair,
Kazuma!
We brought down the Devil Kings
generals together, didn't we?
So, if I don't get to live
in a fancy castle, too,
then it's just not right!
Stop talking, Aqua!
You are confusing
the issue here!
[IRIS] Excuse me.
[ALL] Huh.
Princess Iris.
I'm really sorry.
I couldn't help
overhearing what you said.
Hm.
[DARKNESS] Though he may
be rather pitiful,
in Axel, he has become a fairly
well-regarded adventurer.
There are also those
who consider themselves
his friends
and who worry about him.
Which includes the three of us.
Therefore, I must implore you
to please give him his leave.
[KAZUMA]
You've gotta tell her no, Iris!
"Big Brother is gonna
stay here in the castle
so we can play together!"
[IRIS] You're right.
And I apologize
for being so selfish.
[gasps]
[KAZUMA] Tell em off, Iris,
you've got this!
Come on, you're the only one
with authority
in this whole castle!
What you say goes!
Time to show 'em
who's boss around here!
I was wondering, Lalatina.
[all gasp]
If it would be okay
could I hold
a special going away
banquet for him, tonight?
[all gasp]
[all groaning]
- [thudding]
- [gasps]
[IRIS] Konosuba!
[indistinct chatter]
[AQUA] Hey, hey, Kazuma!
This stuff
is really incredible!
It's all-natural wild melon
that's topped
with some spicy ham!
And it still tastes
super fresh!
This is awesome, too!
Sushi rice with flan on top,
covered in wasabi
and soy sauce!
Yeah, whatever,
good for you guys.
[NOBLE 03-A (M)]
Oh, so beautiful, as always!
Even a rare flower
that only blooms by moonlight
pales in comparison
to your true radiance!
- Yes, indeed!
- You flatter me so.
By the way, have you found
a fiancé yet, Lady Dustiness?
For, if you haven't met
that fortunate man.
What is this?
[NOBLE 03-A (M)] I have sought
her hand for ages now,
so I should receive
preferential treatment!
[KAZUMA] She's a real hit.
- [ALDARP] This is preposterous.
- [gasps]
You see, Lady Dustiness already
has an appropriate partner.
- [ALL] Lord Aldarp!
- [chuckles]
Hey, what the hell
are you even doing here, Pops?
[ALDARP] Shut your mouth!
As a consequence of you
sending the Destroyers core
to my mansion
there are still repairs
that have yet to be finished,
I'll have you know!
I must ask who was the match
for Lady Dustiness
you spoke of?
Still chasing after
Darknesss tail, old man?
That's "Lord Aldarp" to you!
[scoffs]
And there's only one man
who's worthy of taking
the hand of Lady Dustiness
in matrimony.
He's currently doing battle
against the Devil Kings forces
while wielding a sacred sword!
The first prince, Jatice!
[all gasp]
[ALDARP] The kingdom's
champion, Prince Jatice,
and Lady Dustiness,
who has slain
the Devil Kings
generals of late.
What better pairing
could there possibly be?
Yes, that's true.
[NOBLE 03-A (M)] Who could be
better suited to her
than First Prince Jatice?
[indistinct chatter]
[sighs]
Hey, what about the steamy
affair we're having?
Great, Lalatina,
you're just gonna ditch me?
[gasping]
What are you talking about?
Were those intimate moments
just some kinda joke?
You called me "Master"
just the other day...
[grunting]
[all gasp]
I must warn you
all this teasing
could cost you quite dearly!
I'd be careful
if I were you, Lalatina!
Showing how tough
you really are
might just scare
all the boys off...
[screaming]
[all gasp]
[DARKNESS] Oh, my goodness!
You certainly are
a convincing actor!
[indistinct chatter]
[KAZUMA]
I didn't mean any harm.
Well, not much, anyway.
I just saw
how upset Darkness looked
and ended up saying
some weird stuff.
Hey, isn't this supposed
to be my big going-away party?
They're all in there having
a great time without the star!
Well, he's right here,
that's where the star is!
Right here!
[gasps]
Um, shouldn't you be inside,
what are you doing out here?
Iris, you're so amazing!
Being alone at a party
can totally wreck your ego!
Oh, you're the best ever,
little sis!
Come on.
- Hm.
- Huh.
[AQUA] And for my next trick,
I'll take this ordinary glass
right from the table...
She's doing her whole
"performer" thing, again.
[chuckles]
Huh.
After tomorrow, this castle
is going to be so quiet.
Claire won't be upset,
and nobody will be causing
trouble for Rain,
any longer, either.
You make it sound
like a good thing
I honestly have no idea
what you see in me.
Simple...
you aren't like the others.
Everybody dotes on me,
but you never do.
You're rude and so honest.
Though I'm a royal,
you've taught me
such strange things.
You're so immature
and desperate
to win against me.
Hey, I wasn't asking you
to roll out
a huge list of complaints.
I was kinda hoping to find out
all the stuff
you like about me.
Right, and that's exactly what
I've been trying to tell you.
[chuckles]
[KAZUMA]
She's so freaking cute!
[IRIS] With all the time
we've spent together,
I just know it's something
that I'll never forget.
I'm envious of Lalatina.
I'm sure she must enjoy
every single day.
Huh.
[KAZUMA] When tomorrow comes,
she'll start acting like
a princess all over again.
Pretending to be a "good girl"
who never has
a selfish thought.
There's gotta be some way
that I can stay here
at the castle.
[IRIS] Maybe if I could
be an adventurer.
Did you know?
The royal family's
always shown potential in magic
and some other talents too.
So even though
I might not be able
to be a Crusader like Lalatina,
maybe I can still be
a magic user or a priest?
[giggles]
I'd be the kind of adventurer
who'd even surprise you,
Elder Brother!
Or maybe I could choose
to become a thief,
like the one around here
that everybody's been
talking about lately!
[gasps]
But, Claire
would be upset with me
even if I were
only a noble thief.
- [KAZUMA] What'd you say?
- [gasps]
About the noble thief?
Well, uh, there's one
who only targets nobles
with corrupt reputations.
And after every robbery,
they always make
a sizeable donation
to an orphanage
that's run by the Eris Church.
Huh.
Elder Brother?
[KAZUMA] Jackpot baby!
Konosuba!
I would love to spar with you
and then possibly...
- [gasps]
- Darkness!
[KAZUMA]
Oh, good timing, Claire.
W-what are you talking about?
Apparently a thief's been
hassling the nobles
around the capital, right?
That, that's true.
The ones with unsavory
reputations are under fire.
That's about to change!
'Cause I'm nabbing
this "noble thief"!
- Huh?
The same thief
no one's been able
to secure any leads on, whatsoever?
Who is this
unsavory-looking fellow?
Seems unremarkable to me.
[KAZUMA] Uh, thanks guys,
I'm right here ya know.
And I don't care
if his intentions are good!
'Cause a thief is a thief
in my book!
Since when have you had
such a strong sense of justice?
These people need saving
so I'm staying here!
Hey,
you're really unbelievable!
[NOBLE 03-A (M)] Spectacular!
Clearly, you are a comrade
of Lady Dustiness!
Not that I've ever done
anything shameful enough
to dare raise the noble thief's
ire myself, of course.
Nor have I!
I've never once
been unscrupulous!
Thus there'll be no target
aimed at my back.
[KAZUMA] These guys
couldn't be more obvious.
- [gasps]
- Aah!
[KAZUMA] Oh, I get it!
You can't wait to see
your beloved "elder brother"
in action, can you?
Well, just leave it to me!
I'll hang out around
the castle some more
and eventually catch this jerk!
[NOBLE 03-J (M)]
All of us are counting on you
unremarkable lad!
[NOBLE 03-K (M)] I always knew
that boy had it in him!
Do hurry and catch this
disgusting rogue
so we can all rest easier!
What's up? We're gonna
get to keep eating
all this amazing food tomorrow?
Sounds good to me!
I think I'd better start saving
some more room
for that meal, then!
Do you two have any idea
what you are saying?
- Very well, then.
- [gasps]
To catch this noble thief,
Sir Kazuma will first locate
the likely targets,
then be stationed
at their residences.
[gasps]
I must ask each one of you
for your full cooperation!
[shuddering]
[groaning]
[whimpering]
Damn it, how the hell
did I end up here?
[SYLVIA]
I'm touching you on purpose!
I'm touching you on purpose.
It's been a while,
hasn't it, Devil King?
This is your
loyal servant writing
the Growth Chimera, Syl...